A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, Bob Wands, Series 5 FA458
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, 1958-1974; 5
  - Contact Sheets, 1959-1964
    - Contact Sheets, 1959 June-December; D100-D214
      - Miss New York State Fair (Albany), 1959 August 27; D112 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Harness Racing Commission Swear In - Glasser, Farley & Eddy (55th St.), 1959 September 1; D113 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Swear In - James O'Malley as Waterfront Commissioner (55th St.), 1959 September 1; D114 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - National Students' Traffic Safety Com. (55th St.), 1959 September 3; D115 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Small J.D. Meeting (55th St.), September 4; D116 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - NAACP - Life Membership Award (55th St.), 1959 September 3; D117 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Labor Day Parade (NY City), 1959 September 7; D118 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Youth Crime Committee (large group) (55th St.), 1959 September 8; D119 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Chamber of Commerce Dinner (Syracuse), 1959 September 9; D120 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Syracuse State Fair (Syracuse), 1959 September 10; D121 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Aqueduct Opening (NY), 1959 September 14; D122 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Princess Beatrix - Primitive Museum (54th St.), 1959 September 15; D123 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Temple Shaaray Tefila (79th St.- NY City), 1959 September 20; D124 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Mortgage Bankers Association (Commodore - NY City), 1959 September 21; D125 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Limited Profit Housing Corp. (55th St.), 1959 September 21; D126 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Circus - Saints and Sinners (Waldorf), 1959 September 21; D127 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Savings Bond Drive (55th St.), 1959 September 22; D128 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Harvey Firestone & USO (55th St.), 1959 September 22; D129 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Swearing In of Frank DiVotto (55th St.), 1959 September 22; D130 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Joint Defense Appeal of Greater NY (Plaza-NY City), 1959 September 22; D131 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Maple Breakfast - National Life Insurance Company (Commodore), 1959 September 23; D132 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Long Island Press Distinguished Service Award (Garden City), 1959 September 24; D133 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Judge Cohn Testimonial Dinner - Golden Slipper (Glen Clove), 1959 September 24; D134 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Chiefs of Police International Association (Statler-NY City), 1959 September 28; D135 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Bellevue Hospital - Groundbreaking (NY City), 1959 September 28; D136 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - County Officers Association (Grossinger's NY), 1959 September 28; D137 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Civil Defense Directors (Grossinger's NY), 1959 September 28; D138 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Magazine Publishers Association (Commodore - NY City), 1959 September 29; D139 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - National Medical Education Devereaux Josephs Award (Waldorf-NY City), 1959 September 29; D140 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (Plaza-NY City), 1959 September 29; D141 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Swearing In - Com. Isaacson (55th St.), 1959 September 30; D142 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Community Service Society Rally (Biltmore-NY City), 1959 September 30; D143 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - State Youth Camp (Pharsalia, NY), 1959 October 2; D144 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Pulaski Day Parade (41 St. & 5th Ave.), 1959 October 4; D145 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Pulaski Day Dinner (Starlight Roof), 1959 October 4; D146 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Segni Dinner (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 October 4; D147 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Regional Planning Lunch (Roosevelt - NY City), 1959 October 7-9; D148 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Newsreel - Press Room (55th St.), 1959 October 8; D149 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Board of Trade Dinner (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 October 8; D150 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Swearing In - Civil Rights Bureau (55th St.), 1959 October 9; D151 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Employ the Handicapped Luncheon (Plaza - NY City), 1959 October 9; D152 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Columbus Day Dinner (Waldorf), 1959 October 11; D153 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Columbus Day Parade w/Carlino (62 St. & 5th Ave.), 1959 October 12; D154 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Eastern Star (Astor - NY City), 1959 October 14; D155 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Girl Scouts (Plaza - NY City), 1959 October 14; D156 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - President Mateos of Mexico (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 October 14; D157 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Investment Bankers Association (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 October 14; D158 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - YWCA Luncheon (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 October 21; D159 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Al Smith Dinner (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 October 22; D160 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Luncheon at Auburn, NY (Auburn, NY), 1959 October 26; D161 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Cayuga County Republican Club Luncheon (Auburn, NY), 1959 October 26; D162 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Bristol Myers Dedication (Syracuse, NY), 1959 October 26; D163 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - NYS. Education Dinner (Syracuse, NY), 1959 October; D164 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Northway Opening (Albany, NY), 1959 October 27; D165 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - State Police Barracks Dedication (Albany, NY), 1959 October 27; D166 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - NY Republican HQ - Bernard Newman Judicial Candidates (40th St., NY City), 1959 October 28; D167 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - President Sekou Toure of Guinea Primitive Museum (NY City), 1959 November 4; D168 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Gail-Whit Mauzy of Windham NY Ski Resort (55th St.), 1959 November 4; D169 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Federation of Protestant Welfare Luncheon (Roosevelt - NY City), 1959 November 5; D170 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - United Neighborhood Houses of NY Luncheon (St. Regis - NY City), 1959 November 5; D171 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Economic Club Dinner (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 November 9; D172 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - National Conference of Christians & Jews (Biltmore - NY City), 1959 November 11; D173 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - 30th Anniversary - Fund Raising - Dinner (4 Seasons - NY City), 1959 November 16; D174 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - 30th Anniversary - Fund Raising - Reception (Modem Museum), 1959 November 16; D174 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Dinner - Freedom House - Dr. Spaak (Roosevelt - NY City), 1959 November 16; D175 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - World Trade Dinner - Keith McHugh National Foreign Trade Convention (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 November 18; D176 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - American Legion - National Commander Martin B. McKneally (55th St.), 1959 November 19; D177 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Women's National Republican Club Salute to Nelson A. Rockefeller (52nd St. - NY City), 1959 November 19; D178 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - American Legion Dinner (Commodore), 1959 November 19; D179 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Governor Underwood of West Virginia w/Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St), 1959 Npvember 18; D180 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Plane trip to Providence, RI from Marine Terminal (Convair), 1959 November 20; D181 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Press Conferences and TV Panel Show (Sheraton - Biltmore Providence, RI), 1959 November 20; D182 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Rhode Island Republican State Committee Luncheon (Sheraton - Biltmore Providence, RI), 1959 November 20; D183 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - WPRO taped TV show (Providence, RI), 1959 November 20; D184 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - New England Society of Newspaper Editors Dinner (Providence, RI), 1959 November 20; D185 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller in Conference Room Staff Meeting - L. Governor, Murphy, Spad, Corbin, MacCrate (Albany), 1959 November 30; D186 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller in Conference Room with Legislative Leaders - Carlino Mahoney, in corridor w/ R. MacCrate (Albany), 1959 November 30; D187 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Elephants on Governor's Desk (Albany), 1959 November 30; D188 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Little White House Conference for Aging Luncheon (Biltmore), 1959 December 1; D188A (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Civil Defense Meeting Luncheon (Roosevelt - NY City), 1959 December 4; D189 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Swearing In - Joseph Gimma Harness Racing Commission (55th St), 1959 December 4; D190 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Jr. Chamber of Commerce Robert Clark -Lewis Aronowitz (55th St), 1959 December 4; D191 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Rev. Lambert F. Brose - Publisher Armed Services Committee, Lutheran Church (55th St), 1959 December 4; D192 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Morningside community Center Lewis, Robinson, Ellington (55th St), 1959 December 4; D193 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - New York Bible Society Dinner (Waldorf - NY City), 1959 December 4; D194 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Reception for Legislative Leaders (Mansion-Albany), 1959 December 7; D195 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Plane trip from Albany to Newark Airport (Convair 404), 1959 December 8; D196 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Jane Todd Testimonial Dinner - Tom Dewey, W. Rogalin, J. Morehouse (Astor - NY City), 1959 December 9; D197 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (South Bend, IN), 1959 December 12; D198 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (St. Louis, MO), 1959 December 13; D199 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (Minneapolis, MN), 1959 December 14; D200 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (St. Paul, MN), 1959 December 14; D201 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (Madison, WI), 1959 December 15; D202 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (Milwaukee, WI), 1959 December 15; D203 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (Green Bay. WI), 1959 December 16; D204 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (Oklahoma City, OK), 1959 December 17; D205 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (Dallas, TX), 1959 December 17; D206 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (Houston, TX), 1959 December 17; D207 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Seven State Trip (Miami, FL), 1959 December 18; D208 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Plane Trip - Miami to home Guy Savino, Hugh Morrow (en route to NY City), D209 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Press Room (55th St.), 1959 November 18; D210 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Joe Murphy - Tax Bill (Albany), D211 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - NYS. Civil Service Group (Albany), D212 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and political appointee (55th St.), D213 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Businessmen's group and Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), D214 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets, 1960 January-December; D2000-D2126, D2128
      - Negro Soldier at Mansion (Albany), 1960 January 1; D2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - American Helenic Societies of Greater NY Reception - Archbishop Iacovas, Mr. Root Spyros Skouras (10 E 79th St.), 1960 January 21; D2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Governor speaks to legislature (Albany), 1960 January 21; D2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Insurance Department Centennial (Commodore), 1960 January 21; D2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Fireman (Roosevelt), 1960 January 21; D2003A (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Westchester Republican County Committee Dinner - Drop In (Commodore), 1960 January 21; D2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Israeli Ambassador (55th St.), 1960 January 22; D2005 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Carlino, Meyner, Rubicoff (55th St.), D2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Baseball Writers Dinner (Astor), 1960 January 31; D2007 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Portrait of Governor & Mrs. Rockefeller at Mansion (Albany), 1960 February 9; D2008 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Osteopathic Society Luncheon (Waldorf), 1960 February 10; D2009 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Minister of Ghana (55th St.), D2010 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Eye Bank Girl (55th St.), 1960 February 25; D2011 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Monitor Taping, D2011A (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Fallout Shelter - Savings Bank 6th Ave. (49th St. - NY City), D2012 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Conservation Meeting (Music Hall), D2013 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - "Today" Show - NBC - Fallout Shelter - Dave Garroway (NBC - Studio 3), 1960 March 4; D2014 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - YWCA National Board - NY City (600 Lex. Ave.), 1960 March 3; D2015 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Commissioner McHugh "Fallout Shelter" Program (Roosevelt), 1960 March 4; D2016 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Malcolm Wilson's Birthday Party (55th St.), 1960 February 26; D2017 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - TV show - Job Opportunity (Red Room-Albany), 1960 March 10; D2018 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Dinner - United Jewish Appeal (Roosevelt), 1960 March 16; D2019 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - St. Patrick's Day Parade (5th Ave & 63rd), 1960 March 17; D2020 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Mayor Press Conference (55th St), 1960 March 17; D2021 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Boys Town of Italy (55th St.), 1960 March 18; D2022 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Mental Health Group (55th St.), 1960 March 18; D2023 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Press Conference (Red Room-Albany), 1960 February 23; D2024 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Senator Austin's 50 years in government Celebration - Governor & Group (Conference Room-Albany), D2025 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - TV show - Reorganization (Red Room-Albany), 1960 March 24; D2026 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - CBS Show TV "The Great Challenge" (71st & York Ave.), 1960 March 27; D2027 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Press Conference (Red Room-Albany), 1960 March 29; D2028 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Legislative Session - last night (Albany), 1960 March 20; D2029 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Bill Signing (Red Room-Albany), 1960 April 7; D2030 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Jamestown Community College (Jamestown, NY), 1960 April 7; D2031 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Jamestown Hotel - Chautauqua County GOP Committee Dinner (Jamestown, NY), 1960 April 7; D2032 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Groundbreaking of State University College (Stony Brook, LI), 1960 April 8; D2033 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Bill Signing - 2 bills (55th St.), 1960 April 8; D2034 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Bill Signing - Urban League (55th St.), D2035 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Dinner for President and Mrs. Alberto Lieras Camargo of Cambodia (Knickerbocker Club), 1960 April 11; D2036 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Museum at Capital (Albany), 1960 February 12; D2037 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller speaks at annual World Trade Council Pan American Day Luncheon sponsored by Chamber of Commerce (Rochester), 1960 April 13; D2038 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Peruvian Ambassador Fernando Berckemeyer, 1960 April 13; D2039 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Groundbreaking ceremonies at new Kordite Company Plant in Macedon (Macedon, NY), 1960 April 13; D2040 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Groundbreaking ceremonies at the Di-Noc Company of Cleveland Plant (Macedon, NY), 1960 April 13; D2041 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Mayor of Rochester Peter Barry summer home, D2042 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - General Charles de Gaulle (Waldorf - NY City), 1960 April 26; D2043 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Bill Signing story (Albany), 1960 April 28; D2044 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - (inclusive) Bill Signing story (Albany), 1960 April 29 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Wrap-up TV Show (Red Room-Albany), 1960 April 29; D2045 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Local 32B (Astor Hotel - NY City), 1960 May 2; D2046 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Israeli Independence (City Hall Plaza), 1960 May 2; D2047 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Groundbreaking - Fordham University (Lincoln Center - NY City), 1960 May 3; D2048 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Governor Quinn of Hawaii (55th St.), 1960 May 3; D2049 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Wm. Scranton of Pa.- Emmett Hughes (55th St.), 1960 May 3; D2050 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Civil Defense Briefing, Inspection (Peekskill Armory), 1960 May 4; D2051 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Willard State Hospital - Plaque (Ovid, NY), 1960 May 5; D2052 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - NYS Agricultural Station - Cornell (Geneva, NY), 1960 May 5; D2053 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Chamber of Commerce (Seneca Hotel - Geneva), 1960 May 5; D2054 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Japan Society (Hotel Pierre - NY City), 1960 May 23; D2055 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Public Health Conference (Manhattan Center), 1960 May 24; D2056 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Press Conference (Red Room-Albany), 1960 May 25; D2057 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Resignations - Carroll Wainright, Lou Contiguglia (Albany), 1960 May 25; D2058 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Party & Civic Leaders - Kiwanis (Niagara (Lockport)), 1960 May 26; D2059 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - County Chairman Luncheon (Elmira, NY), 1960 May 26; D2060 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Evander Childs High School Pan American Award Assembly (Bronx, NY), 1960 May 26; D2061 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Holstein - Friesian Association (Syracuse, NY), 1960 June 1; D2062 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Automation Conference Dinner (Cooperstown, NY), 1960 June 1; D2063 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Trip to North Dakota (North Dakota), 1960 June 3-5; D2064 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - UJA (56th St.), D2065 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Legion of Honor (French Embassy), 1960 June 8; D2066 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Roosevelt Hotel - Nelson A. Rockefeller Announcement (Roosevelt Hotel), 1960 June 8; D2067 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Anniversary Day Parade Sunday School Union (Brooklyn), 1960 June 9; D2068 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - NMEX man, 1960 June 9; D2069 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - CBS set-up (55th St.), 1960 June 9; D2070 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - British Exhibition - Coliseum - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Prince Philip, VP Nixon (Coliseum - NY City), 1960 June 10; D2071 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - AAA Safety Poster Awards (55th St.), 1960 June 13; D2072 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Hadassah Group & NY State Flag for Israel (55th St.), 1960 June 14; D2073 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Republican State Committee Luncheon (Commodore - NY City), 1960 June 14; D2074 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Dedication ceremonies, new basic science bldg. Roswell Park Memorial Institute (Buffalo, NY), 1960 June 17; D2075 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - National Baptist Convention (Sunday School & Trading Union) (Buffalo, NY Memorial Auditorium), 1960 June 17; D2076 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Heavyweight Championship Fight, Patterson Johansson (Polo Group), 1960 June 20; D2077 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Rotary Luncheon (Binghamton), 1960 June 21; D2078 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - William Hill Home (Union, NY), 1960 June 21; D2079 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Binghamton Flood (Binghamton), 1960 June 21; D2080 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Hill Dinner - Ukrainian Church (Binghamton), 1960 June 21; D2081 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Lake George Inn - dinner after viewing Conservation facilities (Lake Georges), 1960 June 22; D2082 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Whiteface Inn (Whiteface, NY), 1960 June 22; D2083 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Androde - Brazilian journalist (55th St.), 1960 May; D2084A (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Swear-In - Dorothea E. Donaldson-Unemployment Insurance Appeal Board Chair (55th St.), D2084B (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Joseph Carlino Scholarship Dinner - Long Beach Republican Club (Lido Beach), 1960 June 30; D2085 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - African-American Institute - Alhaji the Honorable Sir Ahmadu Bello-Sardauna of Sokoto, Premier of Northern Nigeria & Sir Mohammadu Sanusi, the Emir of Kano (Waldorf), 1960 July 6; D2086 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Henry Wheatley, Nelson A. Rockefeller and Dr. Ronan (55th St.), 1960 July 11; D2087 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Young Republicans' Luncheon (Vincent's Restaurant), 1960 July 12; D2088 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - CBS Interview (55th St.), 1960 July 12; D2089 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - National Republican Presidential Convention (Chicago, IL), 1960 July 23-29; D2090 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - NY Republican Headquarters Opening (Roosevelt), 1960 August 2; D2091 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Press Conference - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Nixon man (55th St.), 1960 August 2; D2092 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - LIRR Strike Settlement - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Mayor Wagner Press Conference (55th St.), 1960 August 3; D2093A (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Swear-In (55th St), D2093B (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - AFL-CIO 3rd Annual Conference (Commodore Hotel), 1960 August 29; D2083B (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Swear-In - Commissioner Sam Aldrich (youth) (55th St.), 1960 September 1; D2095 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Opening of Kings County Republican Campaign Headquarters (Brooklyn), 1960 September 1; D2096 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Ambassador & Mrs. Lodge leave hotel to begin campaign (Waldorf Towers), 1960 September 3; D2097 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Labor Day tour of Beaches - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Lodge (Jones Beach, Rockaway, Coney Island), 1960 September 5; D2098 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Agricultural Dinner - Chamber of Commerce (Syracuse, NY), 1960 September 7; D2099 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - NYS Fair (Syracuse, NY), 1960 September 8; D2100 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - National Urban League Dinner (Commodore Hotel), 1960 September 8; D2101 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Walking Tour - Nelson A. Rockefeller & John Lindsey (NY City), 1960 September 20; D2102 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Hobson Reynolds - Negro Elks (55th St.), 1960 September 21; D2103 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Telephone Pioneers (Madison Square Garden), 1960 September 21; D2104 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Ogdensburg Bridge (St. Lawrence), 1960 September 27; D2105 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Ogdensburg Rotary (Ogdensburg Armory), 1960 September 27; D2106 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Prince Harold of Norway (Metropolitan Club), 1960 September 28; D2107 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Harpur College Dedication (Binghamton, NY), 1960 September 29; D2108 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Mayor Malcolm Ellis (Schenectady, NY), 1960 September 29; D2109 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Swear In - RJ Trainor, DA Westchester County (55th St.), 1960 October 3; D2110 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Avenue of Americas Luncheon (Plaza Hotel, NY), 1960 October 4; D2111 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Howard Jones, Wm. Rand, Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1960 October 7; D2112 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Netherlands Governor Decoration (810 5th-NY City), 1960 October 7; D2113 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Columbus Citizens' Dinner & Parade (Waldorf), 1960 October 11; D2114 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Danish Governor Decoration (55th St), 1960 October 12; D2115 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Al Smith Dinner (Waldorf), 1960 October 19; D2116 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Nixon - Ike Rally (Coliseum), 1960 November 2; D2117 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Loring Electric Dedication of New Building (Bronx), 1960 November 3; D2118 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - NYS. Industrial Research & Development Committee (University Club-NY City), 1960 November 17; D2119 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Bob MacCrate (Albany), 1960 November 28; D2120 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Press Conference (Albany), 1960 November 28; D2121 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Malcom Wilson & World's Fair Committee (55th St.), 1960 December 1; D2122 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller official pictures (55th St.), 1960 December 3; D2123 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Sloan Colt (NY Central president) Pearlman (55th St.), 1960 December 15; D2124 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Chanukah Festival (Madison Square Garden), 1960 December 19; D2125 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - 230 Park Avenue & State Door (230 Park/State Door), 1960 December 8; D2126 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - D2128 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Contact Sheets, 1961 January-July; D3000-D3055
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller addressing Legislature (Albany), 1961 January 4; D3000 (Box 10, Folder 8)